A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.32 (A2006) FA483
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2006.076: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1998-2005; AC.2006.076; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3811-R3815.; 5 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3811-R3815.
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - RESIDENT (Aguilar Rivera, Jose Antonio), 1999-2000 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Al-Azmeh, Aziz) (CO-RESIDENT: Al-Bagdadi, Nadia), 1999-2000 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Alderman, Michael H.), 1999-2001 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Aloysius, Gnanasigiamony), 1999-2001 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Becker, Carol), 1999-2000 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Bedgood, Jill) (CO-RESIDENT: Pelm, Beverly), 1999-2005 (Box R3811)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted - Open in 2026
    - RESIDENT (Bieber, Lorna R.), 1999-2005 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Blanchard, D. Caroline), 1999-2000 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Boege, Eckart), 1999-2000 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Bolkhovitinov, Nikolai Nikolaevich), 1999-2001 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Bowers, John M.), 1999-2000 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Brown, Rexford G.), 2000 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Carter, C. C. Sue) (Co-Resident: Stephen W. Porges; Kerstin Unas-Moberg), 1999-2001 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Carter, Lief Hastings), 1999-2001 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Carty, Elaine McEwan), 1999-2001 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Carvalho, Josely), 1999-2000 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Chambless, Dianne L.) (CO-RESIDENT: Fydrich, Thomas), 1999-2002 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Chase, Oscar G.), 1999-2000 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Chiten, Laurel), 1999-2001 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Clymer, Kenton J.), 1999-2003 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Crawford, Richard), 1999-2001 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Dan, Joseph), 1998-2000 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Danielpour, Richard), 1999-2001 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Datta, Vrinda ) (CO-RESIDENT: Konantambigi, Rajani I, 1999-2001 (Box R3811)
    - RESIDENT (Davis, Robert Charles), 2000-2001 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Dayan, Daniel ) (CO-RESIDENT: Gitlin, Todd), 1999-2001 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (de Solares, Diana), 1999-2000 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Desai, Vishakha N.) (CO-RESIDENT: Poshyananda, Apinian), 1999-2000 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (DeWalt, Kathleen M.), 1999-2000 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Dong, Kui), 1999-2000 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Dmviete, Ina), 1999-2000 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Dubin, Steven C.), 2000 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Epstein, Charles J.), 1999-2000 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Essex, Myron E.) (CO-RESIDENT: Mboup, Souleyrnane), 1999-2003 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Eviner, lnci), 1998-2000 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Fairchild, Bertram H.), 1999-2000 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Fletcher, John Caldwell) (CO-RESIDENT: Wertz, Dorothy Corbett), 1999-2000 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Forster, Keith), 1998-2001 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Freed, Lynn), 1999-2002 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Fried, Robert L.), 1999-2003 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Gal, Joseph), 1999-2000 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Gall, Sally), 1999-2000 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Garrett, George P.), 1999-2000 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Gospel, Howard F.), 1999-2000 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Haines, John), 1999-2001 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Hamilton, Gary G.) (CO-RESIDENT: Kao, Cheng-shu), 1999-2001 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Hartfield, Ronne), 1999-2005 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Havazelet, Ehud), 1999-2000 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Hawkins, Keith Owen) (CO-RESIDENT: Manning, Peter, 1999-2000 (Box R3812)
    - RESIDENT (Hobson, J. Allan) (CO-RESIDENT: Wohl, Hellmut), 1999-2001 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Holland, Martin Jeffrey), 1999-2000 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Hom, Sharon K.) (CO-RESIDENT: Yamamoto, Eric Ken), 1999-2001 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Ivie, David), 1999-2000 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Jackson, William J.), 1999-2004 (Box R3813)
      Restricted - Open in 2025
    - RESIDENT (Javitch, Daniel), 1999-2000 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Jogaratnam, Thambapillai), 1999-2001 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Keil, Julian E.) (CO-RESIDENT: Sutherland, Susan Ellison), 2000-2006 (Box R3813)
      Restricted - Open in 2027
    - RESIDENT (Kelly, Philippa), 1999-2000 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Kertzer, David I.) I, 1999-2002 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Kymlicka, Will), 1999-2000 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Lamont, William Montgomerie), 1999-2000 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Lanctot, Denise Jane) (CO-RESIDENT: Musto, John), 1999-2001 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Lara, Ana), 1999-2001 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Lebow, Richard Ned), 1999-2004 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Lieberman, Ann ) (CO-RESIDENT: Wood, Diane R.), 2000-2003 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (MacAlister, Helen), 1999-2000 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Manley, Rachel), 1999-2000 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Martin, David Alfred), 1998-2000 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Matthews, Michael), 1999-2000 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (McLeod, William Hewat), 1999-2003 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (McQuail, Denis), 1999-2005 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Meyer, Roger Emil), 1999-2001 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Mikhail, William), 1999-2001 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Minnis, Alastair James), 1999-2001 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Molina, Mario Ignacio), 1999-2001 (Box R3813)
    - RESIDENT (Narotzky, Susana E.) (CO-RESIDENT: Smith, Gavin Alderson), 1999-2000 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Neiman, Susan), 1999-2000 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Neuffer, Elizabeth A.), 1999-2003 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Nieto, Sonia), 1999-2003 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Norget, Kristin), 2000-2001 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Obiora, Leslye Amede), 1999-2000 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Pare, Luisa), 1999-2000 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Patterson, Daniel Watkins), 1998-2000 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Pechukas, Philip), 1999-2000 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Pfister, Joel), 1999-2004 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Polcari, Stephen), 1999-2000 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Presser, Harriet B.), 1999-2004 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Rabinowitz, Paula), 1999-2000 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Rehren, Alfredo Jose), 1999-2001 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Robitaille, David Ford), 1999-2001 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Rogers, Pattiann), 1999-2001 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Roll-Hansen, Nils), 1999-2000 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Rowland, Ingrid D.), 1999-2000 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Russell, Peter H.), 1999-2006 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Saffo, Mary Beth), 1999-2000 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Samuels, Richard J.), 1999-2004 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Schaffer, Kay Lois) (CO-RESIDENT: Smith, Sidonie), 1999-2005 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Schnock, Frieder W. M.) (CO-RESIDENT: Stih, Renata), 1999-2001 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Schultz, T. Paul), 1999-2001 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Shapira, Zur B.), 1998-2000 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Sharpley-Whiting, Tracy Denean), 1999-2003 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT (Shrude, Marilyn), 1999-2001 (Box R3814)
    - RESIDENT(Sim, Sorya), 2000-2001 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Simms, Arthur), 1999-2000 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Smith, Gerald Stanton), 1999-2000 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Solovey, Eleonora), 1999-2000 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Sowande, Bode), 1999-2001 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Spicehandler, Ezra) (CO-RESIDENT: Patterson, David), 1999-2001 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Steinkeller, Piotr), 1999-2000 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Sternin, Jen-y), 1999-2000 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Stuart, Dabney), 1999-2004 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Tacuchian, Ricardo), 1998-2000 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Tekce, Belgin), 2000-2001 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Templeton, Fiona), 1999-2000 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Thapar, Romila), 1999-2004 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Urbanczyk, Przemyslaw), 1999-2000 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Vlavianos, Haris), 1998-2001 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Vrebalov, Aleksandra), 1998-2000 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Wesseling, Hertle L.), 1999-2000 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Williams, Charles K.), 1999-2004 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Wollensak, Andrea), 1999-2000 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Xu, Ben ) (CO-RESIDENT: Zhou, Xian), 1999-2001 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Xuejun Wang), 1999-2000 (Box R3815)
    - RESIDENT(Yu-sheng Lin), 1999-2001 (Box R3815)
- AC.2006.083: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2005; AC.2006.083; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, Box R3805.; 1 standard record storage box, Box R3805.
  - Communication for Social Change (CS), AC.2006.083.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 CS 010 - SOUL CITY (SOUTH AFRICA) - RADIO SERIES, "SOUL BUDDYZ 2", 2000-2003 (Box R3805)
  - Food Security (FS), AC.2006.083.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 FS 006 - KASETSART UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - RICE RAGGED STUNT DISEASE, 1999-2004 (Box R3805)
    - 2000 FS 010 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) - ENGINEERING STRIGA-RESISTANT MAIZE, 1999-2005 (Box R3805)
    - 2000 FS 017 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - SALARY SUPPLEMENT FOR PROFESSORIAL CHAIR IN CROPS SCIENCE, 1999-2002 (Box R3805)
    - 2000 FS 025 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - TRANSFORMATION OF RICE FOR ENHANCED SALT TOLERANCE, 2000-2004 (Box R3805)
    - 2000 FS 026 - ZIMBABWE - LANDS AND AGRICULTURE (MINISTRY OF) - IMPROVEMENT OF SOYBEANS AND OTHER LEGUMES, 1999-2005 (Box R3805)
    - 2000 FS 027 - PHILIPPINE RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - BIOTECHNOLOGY FOR RICE IMPROVEMENT FOR FARMERS, 1999-2006 (Box R3805)
    - 2000 FS 038 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - MOLECULAR TAGGING AND INTROGRESSION OF GENES FOR STEMBORER RESISTANCE IN RICE, 1999-2003 (Box R3805)
    - 2000 FS 039 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - FIELD TRAINING; INCREASE SORGHUM PRODUCTION IN DRY FARMING REGIONS, 2000-2003 (Box R3805)
    - 2000 FS 040 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - BANANA RESEARCH, 1993-2003; 2 folders. (Box R3805)
  - Creativity and Culture (CC), AC.2006.083.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2002 CC 058 - MUSEUM OF FINE ARTS, HOUSTON - "RECOVERING THE CRITICAL SOURCES FOR LATIN AMERICAN/LATINO ART" PROJECT, 2002-2003 (Box R3805)
- AC.2006.088: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2003; AC.2006.088; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3806-R3807.; 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3806-R3807.
  - Food Security (FS), AC.2006.088.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2000 FS 041 - AFRICAN CROP SCIENCE SOCIETY (SOUTH AFRICA) - SCIENTIFIC MEETING OF ACSS, 2000-2002 (Box R3806)
    - 2000 FS 043 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - RICE GENETICS AND PATHOLOGY, 1990-2003; 6 folders. (Box R3806)
      - Slides for John O'Toole April 28, 2002, 2006.088.001; 1 Item(s) CD-R
    - 2000 FS 043 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - RICE GENETICS AND PATHOLOGY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1990-2003; 3 folders. (Box R3807)
- AC.2006.092: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1999-2004; AC.2006.092; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, Boxes R3808.; 1 standard record storage box, Boxes R3808.
  - Food Security (FS), AC.2006.092.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 FS 050 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - OVERCOMING CONSTRAINTS TO INCREASED MAIZE PRODUCTION, 2000-2003 (Box R3808)
    - 2000 FS 051 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - OVERCOMING CONSTRAINTS TO INCREASED SWEET POTATO PRODUCTION, 2000-2004 (Box R3808)
    - 2000 FS 052 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - FIELD TRAINING FOR IMPROVED SORGHUM PRODUCTION, 1999-2003 (Box R3808)
    - 2000 FS 054 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - 1RAINING FOR AFRICAN GRADUATE STUDENTS; INTEGRATED PEST MANAGEMENT STRATEGIES FOR SMALL-SCALE FARMERS, 1999-2002 (Box R3808)
    - 2000 FS 055 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - FIELD TRAINING; INCREASE SESAME PRODUCTION IN DRY REGIONS, 2000-2002 (Box R3808)
    - 2000 FS 059 - WEST AFRICA RICE DEVELOPMENT ASSOCIATION (IVORY COAST) - APPLICATION OF ANTHER CULTURE TO THE IMPROVEMENT OF AFRICAN RICE VARIETIES, 1992-2003 (Box R3808)
    - 2000 FS 069 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - FIELD TRAINING; WATER BALANCE IN SEMI-ARID AREAS OF LAKE KYOGA, 2000-2002 (Box R3808)
    - 2000 FS 071 - INTER-AMERICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK - AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH IN LATIN AMERICA AND THE CARIBBEAN, 2000-2006 (Box R3808)
    - 2000 FS 072 - RURAL DEVELOPMENT ADMINISTRATION (KOREA) - MAP-BASED CLONING AND TRANSFORMATION FOR RICE IMPROVEMENT, 1995-2002 (Box R3808)
    - 2000 FS 078 - UNITED STATES - AGRICULTURE (DEPT. OF) - PLANT AND ANIMAL GENOME IX MEETING, 2000-2002 (Box R3808)
    - 2000 FS 079 - PELUM ASSOCIATION (ZIMBABWE) - WORKSHOPS ON SUSTAINABLE LAND USE, 2000-2003 (Box R3808)
    - 2000 FS 080 - SWEDISH UNIVERSITY OF AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES - MASTERS PROGRAMME IN DEVELOPMENT RESEARCH, APPLICATION AND THEORY, 2000-2002 (Box R3808)
    - 2000 FS 087 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - FIELD TRAINING; SNAPBEANS PEST MANAGEMENT, 2000-2003 (Box R3808)
    - 2000 FS 090 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - CROP PRODUCTION TECHNOLOGIES AND FOOD SELF-SUFFICIENCY IN MUMIAS SUGAR SCHEME, 1999-2003 (Box R3808)
- AC.2006.101: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1985-2005; AC.2006.101; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3809-R3810, R3816.; 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3809-R3810, R3816.
  - Food Security (FS), AC.2006.101.1; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - 2000 FS 098 - SHANGHAI ACADEMY OF AG RICULTURAL SCIENCES - RICE TISSU, 1985-2005 (Box R3809)
    - 2000 FS 099 - CHINA NATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - PURCHASE JOURNALS AND PERIODICALS FOR RESEARCH LIBRARY, 1997-2001 (Box R3809)
    - 2000 FS 100 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - SOYBEAN RUST, 2000-2002 (Box R3809)
    - 2000 FS 101 - KENYATTA UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - FIELD TRAINING; NEMATODE CONTROL IN MAIZE CROPPING SYSTEMS, 1999-2002 (Box R3809)
    - 2000 FS 106 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - FIELD TRAINING; INTEGRATED PEST MANAGEMENT FOR COWPEA/GROUNDNUTS, 2000-2002 (Box R3809)
    - 2000 FS 116 - CENTER FOR THE APPLICATION OF MOLECULAR BIOLOGY TO INTERNATIONAL AGRICULTURE (AUSTRALIA) - MAIZE GERMPLASM AND STRIGA RESISTANCE, 2000-2003 (Box R3809)
    - 2000 FS 128 - JOMO KENYATTA UNIVERSITY OF AGRICULTURE AND TECHNOLOGY (KENYA) - FIELD TRAINING; SWEET POTATO RESISTANCE TO WEEVIL, 2000-2004 (Box R3809)
    - 2000 FS 131 - INTERNATIONAL CROPS RESEARCH INSTITUTE FOR THE SEMI-ARID TROPICS (INDIA) - WORKSHOP/TRAINING COURSE ON DROUGHT TOLERANCE AND CEREALS/RICE, 2000-2003 (Box R3809)
    - 2000 FS 134 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - MICROPROPAGATION OF SELECTED BANANA CULTIVARS, 2000-2003 (Box R3809)
    - 2000 FS 136 - MICHIGAN STATE UNIVERSITY - LAND USE PATTERNS AND GENDER IN KENYA, 2000-2003 (Box R3809)
    - 2000 FS 137 - LOKKO, YVONNE - AFRICAN CASSAVA MOSAIC DISEASE, 1997-2002 (Box R3809)
    - 2000 FS 138 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - BIOMETRICS AND APPLIED STATISTICS IN AGRICULTURE, 2000-2003 (Box R3809)
    - 2000 FS 148 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - ORGANIC SOIL FERTILITY MANAGEMENT TECHNOLOGIES, 2000-2005 (Box R3809)
    - 2000 FS 150 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - SOIL FERTILITY MANAGEMENT TECHNOLOGIES, 2000-2005 (Box R3809)
    - 2000 FS 158 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - TRAINING; POTATO PRODUCTION AND RESISTANCE TO LATE BLIGHT DISEASE, 2000-2003 (Box R3809)
    - 2000 FS 162 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - FIELD TRAINING; AGRICULTURAL ECONOMICS AND MARKETING, 2000-2003 (Box R3809)
    - 2000 FS 167 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - FIELD TRAINING; BANANA BIOTECHNOLOGY, 2000-2003 (Box R3809)
    - 2000 FS 171 - CENTER FOR THE APPLICATION OF MOLECULAR BIOLOGY TO INTERNATIONAL AGRICULTURE (AUSTRALIA) - DISSSEMINATE NEW TECHNOLOGIES AND MATERIALS FOR RICE BREEDING, 1999-2002 (Box R3809)
    - 2001 FS 004 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - FIELD TRAINING; BANANA-BASED CROPPING SYSTEMS OF THE LAKE VICTORIA BASIN, 2000-2003 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 006 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - VEGETABLE PRODUCTION, 2000-2002 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 007 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - ON-FARM RESEARCH; TRAINING COURSE, 2000-2002 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 022 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (COLOMBIA) - PARTICIPATORY PLANT BREEDING SYMPOSIUM, 2000-2002 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 023 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - FOOD SECURITY FOR POOR FARMERS IN ZIMBABWE THROUGH STRIGA RESISTANCE, 1997-2002 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 026 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - DISSEMINATION OF SOYBEAN AND MAIZE TECHNOLOGIES, 2000-2003 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 031 - RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (THAILAND) - FIELD SCREENING OF RICE FOR DROUGHT TOLERANCE, 2001-2002 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 033 - (FOOD SECURITY) - DISSEMINATION OF SCIENCE-BASED INFORMATION ON CROP PROTECTION, 2000-2002 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 038 - CUU LONG DELTA RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (VIETNAM) - WORKSHOP ON MARKER-ASSISTED SELECTION AND RICE, 2001-2003 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 040 - TROPICAL SOIL BIOLOGY AND FERTILITY PROGRAMME (KENYA) - CARBON MEASUREMENT AND MODELLING WORKSHOP, 2001-2003 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 051 - THAI RICE FOUNDATION - ASSESS INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY NEEDS OF THE THAI RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE, 2000-2002 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 053 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - GRAIN AND KORTICULTURAL MARKETS FOR SMALLHOLDER FARMERS IN ZIMBABWE, 2000-2002 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 058 - WOOMER, PAUL L. - COLLABORATIVE SOILS RESEARCH IN EAST AND SOUTHERN AFRICA, 1999-2002 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 059 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - MYCOTOXIN CONTAMINATION IN CEREALS AND LEGUMES, 2000-2003 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 060 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (BERKELEY) - BEAHRS ENVIRONMENTAL LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2002 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 063 - INTERNATIONAL SERVICE FOR THE ACQUISITION OF AGRl-BIOTECH APPLICATIONS - INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY NETWORK IN SOUTH EAST ASIA, 2001-2004 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 064 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - FIELD TRAINING; TECHNOLOGY ADOPTION AND RESOURCE MANAGEMENT IN MAIZE PRODUCTION SYSTEMS, 1999-2003 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 070 - UNIVERSITY OF MISSOURI - PLANT AND ANIMAL GENOME X MEETING (COLUMBIA), 2001-2004 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 072 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (NIGERIA) - MUCUNA AS GREEN MANURE COVER CROP, 2000-2003 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 074 - EGERTON UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - DECLINE OF INDIGENOUS CROPS IN WESTERN KENYA, 2001-2002 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 075 - AFRICAN CENTRE FOR FERTILIZER DEVELOPMENT (ZIMBABWE) - AGRO NATURAL RESOURCES MANAGEMENT COUNCIL, 2001-2003 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 079 - NYANKANGA, RICHARD 0. - POTATO LATE BLIGHT DISEASE IN KENYA, 2001-2003 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 083 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - DECISION TOOL FOR BANANA MANAGEMENT WITHIN LAKE VICTORIA BASIN, 2000-2002 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 085 - NATIONAL AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH O.RGANIZATION (UGANDA) - INTEGRATED BANANA PEST MANAGEMENT, 2001-2003 (Box R3810)
    - 2001 FS 086 - KENYATTA UNIVERSITY - NITROGEN LEACHING IN FARMING SYSTEMS IN CENTRAL HIGHLANDS, 2001-2002 (Box R3816)
    - 2001 FS 090 - TROPICA.L SOIL BIOLOGY AND FERTILITY PROGRAMME (KENYA) - SOIL FERTILITY IN TORORO DISTRICT OF UGANDA, 2001-2003 (Box R3816)
    - 2001 FS 092 - WEST AFRICA RICE DEVELOPMENT ASSOCIATION (IVORY COAST) - TRAINING IN INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY PROTECTION AND PATENT PR, 2001-2004 (Box R3816)
    - 2001 FS 096 - (FOOD SECURITY) - CURRICULUM REFORM AT SELECTED AFRICAN UNIVERSITIES, 2001-2003 (Box R3816)
    - 2001 FS 098 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - TRAINING COURSE ON BIOLOGICAL NITROGEN FIXATION, 2001-2003 (Box R3816)
    - 2001 FS 100 - MALAWI - AGRICULTURE AND IRRIGATION (MINISTRY OF) - SUSTAINABLE SOIL FERTILITY MANAGEMENT, 2001-2005 (Box R3816)
    - 2001 FS 102 - NATIONAL CENTER FOR GENOME RESOURCES - BIOINFORMATICS CAPACITY AT CIMMYT, MEXICO, 2001-2003 (Box R3816)
    - 2001 FS 104 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - ECONOMICS AND POLICY WORKING GROUP, 1999-2005 (Box R3816)
    - 2001 FS 106 - TROPICAL SOIL BIOLOGY AND FERTILITY PROGRAMME (KENYA) - WORKSHOPS ON ORGANIC RESOURCE MANAGEMENT TECHNOLOGIES, 2002 (Box R3816)
    - 2001 FS 109 - UNIVERSITY OF DAR ES SALAAM - STUDY AGRICULTURAL SECTOR, ECONOMIC GROWTH AND POVERTY REDUCTION, 2001-2005 (Box R3816)
    - 2001 FS 113 - TROPICAL SOIL BIOLOGY AND FERTILITY PROGRAMME (KENYA) - LATIN AMERICA SOILS CONFERENCE, 2001-2002 (Box R3816)
    - 2001 FS 119 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE OF INSECT PHYSIOLOGY AND ECOLOGY (KENYA) - SOCIOECONOMIC STUDIES, 1997-2004 (Box R3816)
    - 2001 FS 121 - NATIONAL CENTER FOR GENOME RESOURCES - TRAINING IN BIOINFORMATICS, 2001-2002 (Box R3816)
    - 2001 FS 126 - MAHYCO RESEARCH FOUNDATION (INDIA) - 8TH NATIONAL RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY NETWORK MEETING, 2001-2002 (Box R3816)
    - 2001 FS 127 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (BERKELEY) - TRANSGENIC, INSECT RESISTANT COTTON IN ARGENTINA, 2001-2005 (Box R3816)
    - 2001 FS 130 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (COLOMBIA) - INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON COMPARATIVE GENOMICS IN LEGUMES, 2001-2002 (Box R3816)
    - 2001 FS 132 - AFRICARE - INNOVATIVE FARMING IN ZIMBABWE, 2001-2004 (Box R3816)
    - 2001 FS 134 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - EAR ROT INFECTION AND MYCOTOXIN CONTAMINATION IN MAIZE, 2001-2002 (Box R3816)
    - 2001 FS 138 - KENYATTA UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - RODENT PEST MANAGEMENT AND MAIZE CROPPING SYSTEMS, 1999-2003 (Box R3816)
- AC.2006.104: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1997-2004; AC.2006.104; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3817-R3818.; 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3817-R3818.
  - Food Security (FS), AC.2006.104.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2001 FS 139 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - GENETIC ENGINEERING OF RICE FOR RESISTANCE TO PESTS AND DISEASES, 1997-2004 (Box R3817)
    - 2001 FS 142 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER - KIBOS STRIGA RESEARCH FACILITIES REHABILITATION, 2001-2002 (Box R3817)
    - 2001 FS 156 - CITIZENS NETWORK FOR FOREIGN AFFAIRS - IMPROVE ACCESS OF POOR FARMERS IN MALAWI AND ZIMBABWE TO FERTILIZERS, SEEDS AND OUTPUT MARKETS, 2001-2002 (Box R3817)
    - 2001 FS 159 - OMANO, STEVEN WERE - AGRICULTURAL MARKETS AND INSTITUTIONS IN AFRICA, 2000-2004 (Box R3817)
    - 2001 FS 163 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - DATA BASE ON DROUGHT TOLERANCE MAPPING OF RICE, 2001-2003 (Box R3817)
    - 2001 FS 166 - WAGENINGEN AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (NETHERLANDS) - LAND USE CHANGE AND MANAGEMENT IN NAROK DISTRICT OF KENYA, 2001-2003 (Box R3817)
    - 2001 FS 167 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) - CONFERENCE ON LOW-NITROGEN AND DROUGHT TOLERANCE, 2001-2003 (Box R3817)
    - 2001 FS 168 - EGERTON UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - TRAP CROPS AND RESISTANT MAIZE FOR STRIGA CONTROL, 2001-2003 (Box R3817)
    - 2001 FS 169 - INTERNATIONAL FOOD POLICY RESEARCH INSTITUTE - AGRICULTURAL CCONOMICS IN EAST AND SOUTHERN AFRICA, 1939-1947 (Box R3817)
    - 2001 FS 172 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - WEED MANAGEMENT STRATEGIES, 2001-2003 (Box R3817)
    - 2001 FS 174 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - IMPROVED CROP/LIVESTOCK MIXED PRODUCTION SYSTEMS, 2001-2003 (Box R3817)
    - 2001 FS 176 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (NIGERIA) - EIGHTH TRIENNIAL INTERNATIONAL SYMPOSIUM ON TROPICAL ROOT AND TUBER CROPS, 2001-2003 (Box R3817)
    - 2001 FS 180 - EGERTON UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - WORKSHOP ON LAND USE IN LAKE NAIVASHA AREA, 2001-2004 (Box R3817)
    - 2001 FS 182 - SWISS FEDERAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY (SWITZERLAND) - VITAMIN A AND IRON IN VIETNAMESE RICE, 1999-2003 (Box R3817)
    - 2002 FS 001 - (FOOD SECURITY) - MARKETS FOR INCREASED FARMER INCOMES IN AFRICA, 2001-2002 (Box R3817)
    - 2002 FS 007 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE OF INSECT PHYSIOLOGY AND ECOLOGY (KENYA) - EVALUATION OF SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH RELATED TO INTEGRATED PEST MANAGEMENT, 2002-2003 (Box R3817)
    - 2002 FS 011 - AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH COUNCIL (SOUTH AFRICA) - THIRD INTERNATIONAL BACTERIAL WILT SYMPOSIUM, 2001-2002 (Box R3817)